提供了一些实用类型和
&gt;&gt; Mike North: TypeScript comes
with a couple Utility Types and
他们最近增加了一对夫妇，严重依赖于这个条件。
they have recently added a couple more
that heavily depend on this conditional.
第一个是偏爱。
Number one is Partial.
Partial 只是使得类型上的所有内容都是可选的。
Partial just makes everything
on a type optional.
这是伟大的，如果你有一个选项对象。
This is great if you
have an options object.
你可能有一组默认值
Where you have maybe a set of defaults and
有人可以给你这些选项的子集。
someone can pass you
a subset of those options.
你只需要做一个物体合并，就像一个大的啪嗒声。
And you just wanna do sort of
an object merge, like a big splat.
所以无论给予什么,
So take whatever is given,
合并到我的备用计划里，你就有了全部的选择。
merger it into my fallbacks and
you have the full set of options.
所以 Partial 在姓名和电子邮件旁边打了个问号，它可能有电子邮件。
So Partial has put a question mark next
to name and email, it may have email.
Pick 允许我们选择一个或多个属性。
Pick allows us to select one or
more properties of something.
所以我创建了一个类型叫 HasThen,
So, I've created a type called HasThen,
它接受一个类型参数，然后从一个承诺中选择一个，然后接住。
it takes a type parameter and it's going
to pick of a promise, then, and catch.
让我们看看，我使用的类型,
So let's see, so then I'm using the type,
我正在挣脱承诺，解决问题，然后抓住它。
I'm extracting off of promise.resolve
just, then, and catch.
所以它们就在那里，如果我只是抓住它们，我们只能看到它们。
And so there they are, if I were to
just grab then we would only see then.
如果我把事情简单化,
If I'd made this a little simpler,
迈克 · 诺斯: 那么我们这里就不需要模板了。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Then we don't
need the template here.
迈克 · 诺斯: 我没有初始化它，但是
&gt;&gt; Mike North: I didn't initialize it, but
我们只能看到 a 是现在，Mike North: 只能看到 b
we can see only a is present,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Only b should
在这里，或者你可以做 b 或 a，他们都应该在场。
be present here, or you can do b or
a and they should both be present.
所以你是在通过属性键来选择对象类型。
So you're picking off of
an object type by property key.
迈克 · 诺斯: Extract 让我们，当你有一个大的交叉点类型它会
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Extract lets us, when
you have a big intersection type it'll
让你选择可以分配给特定类型的东西。
let you select things that
are assignable to a particular type.
所以只给我字符串，我在这里错误地命名了。
So give me only strings,
I misnamed this here.
数字，只给我数字。
Number, gives me only numbers.